https://www.capriflavors.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Log In
Join Our Mailing List to Getthe Latest News & Specials
Categories
Bakery & Pastry ... Bakery & Pastry IngredientsBreadBreadsticks - Crackers - Taralli - Potatoes ChipsBazaarBest Pizza Preparation ProductsBeverage - Soft Drinks - BibiteBooks_ Magazines and photosCheeseChristmas BasketChristmas: Cakes & Gift ... Balocco Pandori, Panettoni, & Christmas CakesBarbieroBauli ChristmasChiostro di SaronnoCondorelli ChristmasCrispoDal ColleNougat & Chocolate SpecialtiesVerganiCoffee ... Barley-Tea-Hot Cocoa-CappuccinoBiancaffe SpecialsBORBONECoffee SyrupsDrip CoffeeEspresso - Caffè ... CapsulesGround Espresso - Caffe' MacinatoWhole Beans - In GraniCoffee ESE Pods - Cialde Caffe' EspressoEspresso Makers ... Milk & Cappuccino FrostherNapoletana (Drip coffee)Stovetop EspressoCondimentsCookies - Biscotti ... Balocco CookiesBistefani CookiesDoria CookiesMasini CookiesMellin CookiesMulino Bianco CookiesPavesi CookiesPlasmon CookiesEaster Cakes and Chocolate EggsFerreroForno BonomiFresh PastaFrozen Dessert ... Bindi Frozen cakes- store pickupBindi Frozen Cheese CakesBindi Frozen Single Portions -Fruits & NutsGift CertificatesGift IdeasGluten FreeKitchen UtensilsMeatMini Cakes ... Cakes: Mini Desserts -Croissant -Snacks -MerendineMulino BiancoOlive Oil: FlavoredOlive Oils: Special Extra Virgin SelectionOlivesOreganoPasta - Gnocchi - Rice ... GnocchiPasta ... Balzano PastaBarbieroBarillaColacchioDe CeccoGarofalo Signature PastaGranoroLa Casa del Grano PastaLa Pasta Donna InesLuciana Mosconi Egg PastaOrogialloPrimeluci PastaPrometeo Urbino Farro PastaTarall'Oro PastaViva ItaliaRice & RisottoSeviroli Frozen pastas ... Store Pickup OnlyPesto Sauces - Bruschetta SpreadPolentaSantalSauceSeafoodSeasoning & SaltSoupsSweet ... Candied FruitCandies - Confetti - Chewing Gum ... AmarelliCandies in BulkCedrincaCrispo Confetti & SpecialitesPerfetti Brands: Alpenliebe - Brooklyn - GoliaPeruginaSperlariCandy JelliesChocolate - CioccolatoChocolate: Nutella - Hazelnut & Pistachio SpreadForno BonomiNougat - TorroneNovi ChocolatePreseves -Jam -Mostarda -HoneyTOMATOES ... Canned TomatoesSan Marzano Tomato DOPTOMATO SAUCE & PUREETUTTO CALABRIAVegetables & BeansVinegar & Vincotto ... VincottoVinegar ... BALSAMIC VINEGAR OF MODENAWINE and RED VINEGARSpecials ...Featured Products ...
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site.
It will cover the following information:
What personal information is collected from you through the use of our web site, how it is used, and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your personal data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing:
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site.
We are the only ones that have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact.
We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to communicate with you.
We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to
fulfill your request (e.g. to ship an order).
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to keep you informed about specials,
new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information:
You may opt out of any future contact from us at any time.
You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security:
We take a variety of precautions to protect your information.
When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and
transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser,
or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline.
Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted
access to personal information. The computers/servers in which we store your personal information are kept in a secure
environment.
Credit card numbers are not stored anywhere on our site. They are only used to process your order at the time of the
order.
If you have questions about this privacy policy or have concerns about how we are using your personal information, you should Contact Us.
Shop by Brand
Please Select
Acetaia Malagol..
Aceto Balsamico..
Agostino Recca
Amarelli
Ambrosio
Amica chips
Antica Torroner..
Antico Torronif..
Antimo Caputo
Antonio Mozzare..
Artibel
As Do Mar
Balconi
Balocco
Balocco Christm..
Balocco Easter
Balzano
Barbiero
Barilla
Barra Vincenzin..
Bonta' di Pugli..
Chiostro Di Sar..
Delicious Desse..
Della Marca Pas..
Fratelli Berett..
Frutto d`Italia
Galleffi efferv..
Garofalo Pasta
Ghiott
Gia
Gianni Calogiur..
Le Colline di E..
Le Delizie di C..
Orti di Calabri..
Perfetti - Alpe..
S.A.TOS Societa..
::
FAQ's
::
Privacy Statement
::
Contact Us
Comodo SSL
Copyright © 2020 Capri Flavors. [104.193.142.50] 12/11/20 12:47:23
